Dental Alumni Notes [News] UP116
Digital Collections and Archives, Tufts University
Dental Alumni Notes [News]
1961 -- 1996
Digital Collections and Archives, Tufts University
School of Dental Medicine
UP116
0.5 Linear Feet
Arrangement
This collection is organized into one series.
Scope and Contents
This collection contains issues of Tufts Dental Alumni News, later known as Alumni Notes, published by the Alumni of Tufts University School of Dental Medicine. Contains news for Dental School Alumni. Published twice a year. It contains issues from 1961-1968 and 1982-1996.
Biographical / Historical
Tufts University School of Dental Medicine was established in 1868 as Boston Dental College. It was incorporated into Tufts College in 1899. Although founded as a school to educate students from New England, today Tufts is renowned throughout the United States and the world as a center for academic and clinical excellence. Tufts boasts over 6,900 alumni composed of individuals from all fifty states and thirty-nine countries. The majority of the alumni outside of the USA have completed an Advanced Education Certificate program. Students receive a comprehensive education emphasizing the importance of didactic coursework, clinical experience, and practice management that prepares them to enter the work force as confident, proficient clinicians.
- Dental Alumni Notes [News], 1961 -- 1996; UP116.001; 0.5 Linear Feet
  Scope and Contents
  This series contains issues of Tufts Dental Alumni News, later known as Alumni Notes, published by the Alumni of Tufts University School of Dental Medicine. Contains news for Dental School Alumni. Published twice a year. It contains issues from 1961-1968 and 1982-1996.
  Arrangement
  This series is arranged chronologically.
  Conditions Governing Access
  Open for research.
  - Dental Alumni News, 1961-02; UP116.001.001.00001 (Box 1)
  - Dental Alumni News, 1962-03; UP116.001.001.00002 (Box 1)
  - Dental Alumni News, 1963-03; UP116.001.001.00003 (Box 1)
  - Dental Alumni Notes, 1968-02; UP116.001.001.00004 (Box 1)
  - Dental Alumni Notes, 1982-09; UP116.001.001.00005 (Box 1)
    Volume, issue
    3, 3
  - Dental Alumni Notes, 1983-01; UP116.001.001.00006 (Box 1)
    3, 4
  - Dental Alumni Notes, 1983-03; UP116.001.001.00007 (Box 1)
    3, 5
  - Dental Alumni Notes, 1985-10; UP116.001.001.00008 (Box 1)
    6, 1
  - Dental Alumni Notes, 1985-01; UP116.001.001.00009 (Box 1)
  - Dental Alumni Notes, 1986-01; UP116.001.001.00010 (Box 1)
  - Dental Alumni Notes, 1986-09; UP116.001.001.00011 (Box 1)
  - Dental Alumni Notes, 1987-02; UP116.001.001.00012 (Box 1)
  - Dental Alumni Notes, 1987-09; UP116.001.001.00013 (Box 1)
  - Dental Alumni Notes, 1988-02; UP116.001.001.00014 (Box 1)
  - Dental Alumni Notes, 1988-09; UP116.001.001.00015 (Box 1)
  - Dental Alumni Notes, 1989-03; UP116.001.001.00016 (Box 1)
  - Dental Alumni Notes, 1989-09; UP116.001.001.00017 (Box 1)
  - Dental Alumni Notes, 1990-03; UP116.001.001.00018 (Box 1)
  - Dental Alumni Notes, Fall, 1990; UP116.001.001.00019 (Box 1)
  - Dental Alumni Notes, Winter, 1991; UP116.001.001.00020 (Box 1)
  - Dental Alumni Notes, Fall, 1991; UP116.001.001.00021 (Box 1)
  - Dental Alumni Notes, Spring, 1992; UP116.001.001.00022 (Box 1)
  - Dental Alumni Notes, Fall, 1992; UP116.001.001.00023 (Box 1)
  - Dental Alumni Notes, Spring, 1993; UP116.001.001.00024 (Box 1)
  - Dental Alumni Notes, Fall, 1993; UP116.001.001.00025 (Box 1)
  - Dental Alumni Notes, Summer, 1994; UP116.001.001.00026 (Box 1)
  - Dental Alumni Notes, Winter, 1995; UP116.001.001.00027 (Box 1)
  - Dental Alumni Notes, Fall, 1995; UP116.001.001.00028 (Box 1)
  - Dental Alumni Notes, Spring, 1996; UP116.001.001.00029 (Box 1)